No way...
His bonus is
three million?
My loser ex-husband
just turned into
a damn millionaire?!
This has to be fake.
You two are putting on a show for us.
So the Eagles want to bring back a fired coach?
Let me guess...
Your team's
performance sucked.
You fumbled
all the tactics,
and now you want
Ted to come
and save your ass, right?
Bullshit.
You only got a few tricks from me.
Only a shit team
like yours
would treat him like he's some kind of genius.
Judging by your
recent record,
looks like our shit team
could wipe the floor
with you.
With ease, bitch!
Just wait, Ted.
When I beat you,
even if you come
crawling back,
I'll slam the door
in your face!
Hey,
the Knights will
never lose to you.
Eagle!
The Knights, who once sat dead last
in the league, have made a miracle run
all the way to
the semifinals.
But today, they face the powerhouse Eagles.
Will this be the end of their story?
Let's stay tuned for a fantastic game to come.
Eagle!
Fight!
Knights!
Okay, boys, come on.
Take a knee.
Listen up!
I know that team over there is strong. Alright?
No one expects us to win.
Now, I promise you...
This team will go down
if we run my plays.
We will walk out of here with a win.
I can promise you that.
Yes, sir.
Coach,
we trust you completely.
Alright, fellas,
let's go get this win.
Alright, boys, bring it in.
Hands in the middle.
Barton, swing's on you.
Alright, one on three,
one on me.
One, two, three. Win!
Let's go, boys! Let's go!
Ted, I know you're gonna work miracles for me.
The beer is just not
suitable for a
game of this caliber.
It's for poor people.
People of class.
Like... like us.
Need whiskey or...
wine.
West, how confident are you in this game?
I got a bowl of money riding on us.
I need a win.
Relax.
This is a sure win.
I will make sure you get your money.
Their team's
combined worth
is thirty million dollars.
This guy right here?
Forty million.
How are they supposed to compete with that?
Well,
as you know, I don't give a fuck about football.
But I do care
about winning.
I'm counting on you to get this across the line.
To victory.
Celebrating way
too soon, coach.
Get him!
Block up!
Come on, block!
Push through!
Block!
There we go!
Good, good!
Touchdown!
Right from the start,
the Knights are off to a blazing start.
Scott drives it home for the first touchdown!
What the fuck
is happening?